It’s… raining.
Yeah, it is.
It may be raining, but I’m going to try my best to increase the number of confetti in the bottle!
Whew! That was close.
Do…ba…to!
I got all muddy because of you!
I-It doesn’t matter that you got dirty, Ioryogi-san.
The rain will wash it all away.
It does matter!
I’ll still get soaked.
Kobato-chan?
Good morning.
Sayaka-sensei!
Um… Sayaka-sensei?
What is it?
Where are we going?
To your home.
Huh?
Right here.
But is it really okay for me to live here?
Yes, if you want to.
Now, let’s go inside.
Yes!
Let me introduce you.
Chitose is my friend and the landlady of these apartments.
Oh, nice to meet you. I’m Hanato Kobato.
Kobato-san, is it? Nice to meet you too. I’m Mihara Chitose.
If there’s anything you don’t understand or have questions about, just ask me.
Yes!
Chitose, I’ll leave the rest to you.
See you later, Kobato-chan. I have to go back to the preschool.
Y-Yes, thank you very much.
I’ll come by later to help out.
That Sayaka… always worrying about other people.
Kobato-san?
Yes!
I’m counting on you.
She seems so nice!
Shouldn’t you say, “I’ll be in your care from now on?”
You’ll be in my care from now on.
Not in your care.
When will your belongings arrive?
Eh! Umm…
This is all I have.
What about your futon?
I don’t have one.
I see… Then, I’ll show you around.
Yes!
Such a wonderful building.
Thank you.
Isn’t this a wonderful room, Ioryogi-san?
Ioryogi-san?
Huh?
I wonder where he went?
Dobato…
Do you like leaving me behind?!
I’ve told you! I’m just a stuffed animal here!
I’m sorry!
Geez…
Hey…
Y-Yes!
Preschool is starting soon.
That’s right!
I have to hurry… I’ll be late!
I’m sorry. Are you all right?
I’m fine.
On the other hand, this guy…
I’m sorry. It got all wet.
It’s kinda cute.
There. Now it’s all clean.
Here.
See ya!
Thank you so much!
She is a lot kinder than you are.
Kobato-chan.
Did you like the room?
Yes! It has a roof and a well-made floor. It's wonderful.
Really? That’s good to hear.
Kobato-chan!
Oh?
Play with us!
I’m cleaning right now.
Then, I’ll help.
We’ll help too!
Thank you!
What should I do?
Let’s see.
Hey, what about me?
You didn’t have to provide her with an apartment.
But since she came here, everyone’s looked so happy.
You shouldn’t be so cold to her.
You always do this…
How many times do you have to get hurt?
Good point…
These days, you need to be careful when forming new relationships.
Thank goodness the rain stopped, huh?
The preschool is closed tomorrow, so let’s work hard to collect more confetti, Ioryogi-san!
The weather was clear just a moment ago…
That’s why I told you to bring an umbrella.
I’m sorry.
It doesn’t look like it’s going to stop anytime soon.
No choice but to go and get wet then.
Ah, that’s not fair! You get to stay dry!
You don’t have an umbrella?
No…
Here.
You can use this if you want to.
But…
You can have it.
It belonged to a customer.
Um… I’ll bring it back once the rain stops.
All right, I’ll be waiting.
Yes! Thank you very much.
Kobato, you dealt with that as a normal person would.
So, if you go on like this…
Yes!
This is where I’ll find information on who needs to be healed!
Somehow, that makes sense.
People come and go here a lot.
I’m going to do my best!
I wasn’t able to find out anything…
What’s wrong?
The umbrella I borrowed is gone!
What?
Someone might have taken it by accident.
They took it for their own convenience.
Eh? Is it okay to take other people’s umbrellas?
Of course it isn’t!
Oh no. The umbrella the cake shop owner lent to me…
Oh?
We meet again.
Ah! The one from yesterday…
What’s wrong?
I lost my umbrella.
Here.
I’ll lend you mine.
But…
It’s okay! My house is just around the corner.
If you don’t have an umbrella, he’ll get wet too.
Right?
Tadokoro?
If you eat too many sweets, you’ll get fat.
Be quiet! Katsuragi, you idiot!
Wait!
Um…
Thank you!
I’ll hit you if you don’t wait up!
Won‘t you hit me either way?!
What was that?
Katsuragi!
She’ll get wet, but she still lent me her umbrella.
Good morning.
Good morning, Kobato-san.
Oh?
You have a mark on your face from the tatami.
Huh?
I-I’m off!
Oh! Having this mark on my face is so embarrassing.
She must be thinking strange things about me now.
Ah!
Good morning!
Huh?
Thank you for the umbrella.
You knew where my school is?
Yes!
When I went to apologize at the cake shop,
I was told that the green uniforms belonged to this school.
Ioryogi-san is thankful too.
Ioryogi-san?
Yes!
Oh, you mean this stuffed animal.
What an interesting name.
My name is Hanato Kobato.
I’m Tadokoro Mutsumi.
Tadokoro.
Your hair is sticking up in the back.
Be quiet! That’s none of your business!
Where is it?
It’s all right.
I have a tatami mark on my face.
That’s because you didn’t cover it.
I-I'm sorry…
Don’t worry about it.
Well, I have morning practice.
That boy seemed a little unkind, didn’t he?
He’s just like Fujimoto-san.
Oh no! If I'm late, he’ll get mad at me again!
You’re a minute and 23 seconds late.
O-One minute?
One minute late is still late.
I-I’m sorry…
Did you sleep too much?
The tatami mark is gone now.
It’s because of the futon jutting out, huh?
I don’t have a futon.
What?
Good morning, Kobato-chan.
G-Good morning.
Did Fujimoto-kun say something mean to you?
Um… I…
He’s a bit blunt, but he’s not bad.
But if he bullies to you, please tell me.
I’ll give him a beating!
B-Beating?
Yes. Just like old times.
Old times?
Hey! It’s finally sunny outside, so let’s air the futons.
Oh, yes! I’m coming!
Goodbye, Kobato-chan.
Yes! Goodbye!
It looks like it’s going to rain again.
Kobato-chan, do you have an umbrella?
I don’t.
Fujimoto-kun does. You should leave together.
I have plans after this. Take my umbrella and go.
I don’t want to share it with you.
Share an umbrella?
It’s when two people get under one umbrella…
It’s just as Sayaka-sensei said.
It really did start to rain.
The umbrella that someone accidentally took is back.
Eh, Kobato-chan?
We meet again.
Oh, Tadokoro Mutsumi-san.
Mutsumi is fine. What’s going on?
My umbrella’s back.
I see! That’s good!
Yes! Are you shopping again?
Yup! My stomach always grumbles after a hard kendo practice.
You’re really trying hard, aren’t you?
Yeah, but…
I can’t eat too much or I’ll get fat.
I’ll give you this.
Are you sure?
It’s okay.
Here! See you.
Oh! So that’s “sharing an umbrella,” right?
Mutsumi-san?
Mutsumi-san…
…looked really sad.
What can I do to cheer her up?
Who knows. That looked rather complicated.
Good evening! Please open the door…
Yes?
A-Are you all right?
Yes.
Sorry to disturb you.
Nice to meet you. I’m the landlady’s daughter, Chiho.
And I’m Chise.
Nice to meet you too. I’m Hanato Kobato.
You don’t have a futon, right?
Ah, yes.
Mama said you can use this if you want.
Really?
She also said that it’s been used before.
Well, see you later.
Thank you very much!
They gave me a futon.
You are supposed to heal, not be healed yourself.
That’s right.
I will cheer up Mutsumi-san.
How?
W-Well, I’ll do my best!
Hey, what are you going to do?
I think it’s best to leave her alone for now.
Ah!
Excuse me!
Huh?
I-I have something to tell you.
It’s about Mutsumi-san.
Please!
What do you mean?
Please share an umbrella with Mutsumi-san too.
Please.
What do you mean, “with Mutsumi-san too?”
I suppose it’s impossible.
Mutsumi-san!
What are you doing?
Mutsumi-san looked so sad yesterday…
…when you were sharing an umbrella with another girl.
I wasn’t really…
Then, why?
That’s…
If I did something I shouldn’t have, I'm sorry.
It’s just that I wanted to cheer up Mutsumi-san.
That’s why…
Here! Share an umbrella with Mutsumi-san!
Kobato-chan?
Please.
I’d feel bad for that girl.
Get under it.
W-What? It’s all right if you don’t.
I’m not going out with her.
She… just forgot her umbrella,
so we went home together.
See, Mutsumi-san.
Just get under it already. I’m leaving.
Katsuragi!
Wait up! I’m getting wet!
Move over a bit.
Don’t complain.
There’s no room.
Look…
But it’s the truth.
Even if you tell me to move over, the umbrella is still small…
Mutsumi-san still doesn’t look very happy.
It’s fine that way.
Really?
It’s strange, isn’t it, Ioryogi-san?
What is?
There’s one more confetti now…
But you healed her for that very purpose, didn’t you?
I just wanted to cheer Mutsumi-san up, so I helped her out.
Well, you healed her broken heart even if you didn’t mean to.
Really?
The extra confetti in there is the very proof of it.
Then that’s good!
I can see that this isn’t going to be easy.
The presence I just felt…
What’s wrong, Kohaku?
No, it’s nothing, Shuichiro-san.
Let’s go.
You did good this time, so I think I’ll give you high points.
Really?
A-Are you all right, Ioryogi-san?
Do…ba…to!
Zero points!
That’s mean, Ioryogi-san. You said you would give me high points just now!
Because of you, I am always getting soiled with mud or ink or whatever!
It’s okay. The rain will wash it all away.
It won’t wash away my anger!
No way!